# **Chelsey Machin**

# Full-Stack Developer

Multi-talented full-stack developer with a background in social work and more recently IT. Self-starting career switcher that will have two full degrees under my belt by 28. Incredibly motivated to learn and grow through any means available. Customer service competent with lots of modern technical skills and experience. In my personal projects, I am enjoying playing around with React, different modern CMS, and a good variety of different libraries, frameworks, and publicly available APIs out there. Please peek at my GitHub or portfolio for current personal projects and schoolwork.

### **Contact**

### **Address**

Tacoma, WA, 98406

### Phone

(360) 979-7099

#### Email

chelseymachin@gmail.com

### **GitHub**

@chelseymachin

### LinkedIn

**Chelsey Machin** 

### **Portfolio**

Online Portfolio

### **Skills**

- HTML / CSS / JavaScript
- C++ / Java / Python
- o GIT / Bash / PowerShell
- Jira & general ticketing
- MySQL / GROQ
- o Adobe Design Suite
- o ZenDesk Slack Teams
- Microsoft Office suite
- o Technical documentation
- Automated testing (Mocha)
- o CMS Administration

# **Education**

### **University of Washington**

Bachelor of Arts in Social Welfare

### **Western Governor's University**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Graduation Date: December 2021

## **Work History**

#### November 2020 - Current

### **IT Help Desk**

Burkhart Dental Supply – Tacoma, WA

- o SME for all business applications; first point of contact for all IT inquiries
- Maintain ticketing system for all incoming requests and technical inventory management
- o Initial troubleshooting for database, server, site, and hardware functionality
- Develop and manage interdepartmental tickets (Development tickets, Marketing tickets, etc.)
- Maintain Active Directory, mail permissions, and application permissions for 400+ employees

### January 2019 - November 2020

### **Technical Program Coordinator**

Tacoma Community College - Tacoma, WA

- Submitted and monitored technical tickets for state accounting software
- Worked with State Board of Technical and Community Colleges to help establish best business practices for new software implementation
- Trained other departments and schools on program functionality, processes, and troubleshooting
- Achieved subject matter expert recognition from SBCTCC for work in specific customer-facing module of state accounting software
- Managed all 3rd party billing and payment for student accounts
- o Tracked internal spending of special/term-limited funding programs
- Interfaced with students and vendors regarding billing and software use/access

### **August 2017 – February 2019**

### **Legal Assistant**

LGBS, LLP - Gig Harbor, WA

- o Updated company software with skip trace results
- Supported administration and research processes for civil litigation cases
- Managed all administrative tasks for firm partners and associates
- Generated leads to meet and exceed revenue goals by identifying new clients
- Answered telephone and maintained email correspondence with all clients and vendors
- Worked with court vendors to establish client guidelines